Gregg Stubberfield

Web Developer

About Me

Front End Web Developer with **3+ years** experience designing, developing, and testing responsive websites with an array of technologies. Aspiring to broaden my technical skills to become a more adept developer.

Contact



850.305.9090



1208 Kathy Drive Yardley PA 19067



StubberG3@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/stubberg3/

Skills

Javascript (ES6, jQuery)	5 years
HTML5	5 years
CSS (Materialize)	5 years
Git	5 years
C	3 years
C++	3 years
Python	1 year

Hobbies

Super Smash Brothers Ultimate Player
Sponsored by Bento Boy Gaming

Sponsored by Bento Box Gaming

Star Realms Deck-Building Game Platinum Tier on BoardGameGeek Running (5K)

Education

B.S. Mathematical Sciences | **Minor: Computer Science** University of West Florida | 2015 | **GPA: 3.5**

Experience

Web Development and Support Specialist

Innovative Software Solutions, Inc.

Maple Shade, NJ | November 2017 - Present

- » Develop responsive design websites and user interfaces for over 20 clients
- Collaborate across departments to translate client requirements and meet expectations
- Direct creative design standards by creating UI templates that are utilized by the team

Client Service Representative

Innovative Software Solutions, Inc.

Maple Shade, NJ | February 2017 - November 2017

- Provided technical support and maintained an average of 20 clients monthly, exceeding company standards on customer satisfaction and volume
- Answered emails and calls daily, resulting in being awarded for the most closed incidents in the department
- Trained new employees on company software and Microsoft Office tools to increase their productivity

Private Tutor

Tutordelphia

Philadelphia, PA | August 2016 - November 2017

- Tutored clients of various ages in subjects ranging from mathematics, computer science, and physics
- >> Prepared clients for exams such as the ACT, SAT, and ASVAB
- Collaborated with clients to identify their weakness and strengths, developing tutoring sessions that fit to their individual needs

Honors and Awards

Burr Research Fellowship

University of West Florida | 2015

Using a combination of interview and examination data taken from the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (NHANES), took a Structural Equation Modeling approach to researching factors affecting physical activity in children

Holly Guiles Mathematics Achievement Award

Northwest Florida State College | 2012

Awarded for demonstrating a genuine passion for mathematics and helping students succeed in their education

Extracurricular

Vice President

University of West Florida Mathematical Association | 2014 - 2015

President

Northwest Florida State College Asian Pop Culture Club | 2013 - 2014

Secretary

Society of American Military Engineers | 2012 - 2013